In the last lesson we talked about how to have a discussion very very important in everyday English
在上一课中，我们讨论了如何在日常英语中进行非常非常重要的讨论
especially if you want to have better friendships right.
特别是如果您想拥有更好的友谊。
In this lesson though we're going to talk about how you explain things not only how we describe things
在本课中，虽然我们将讨论你如何解释事物，而不仅仅是我们如何描述事物
in detail but how we connect our memories to those things how we connect our emotions to those things.
细节，但我们如何将我们的记忆与这些事物联系起来，我们如何将我们的情绪与这些事物联系起来。
Remember earlier in the course we talked about descriptions.
记得在课程的前面我们谈到了描述。
This will be connected to that but we're going to also connect our feelings to the descriptions that
这将与此相关，但我们还将我们的感受与描述相关联
we give and when we do that what we basically if it's about an event or if it's about things that happened
我们付出，当我们这样做时，我们基本上是关于一个事件或发生的事情
to us in the past we call that a story.
过去对我们来说，我们称之为故事。
And stories are a very deep part of human culture a very deep part of how humans how people talk to
故事是人类文化的一个非常深刻的部分，是人类如何交谈的一个非常深刻的部分
each other.
彼此。
So I believe this is just my opinion.
所以我相信这只是我的看法。
I believe that stories are everywhere around us even in our daily lives.
我相信，即使在我们的日常生活中，故事也无处不在。
I believe that you tell stories much more than you think you actually do.
我相信你讲的故事比你想象的要多得多。
That's what I believe.
这就是我所相信的。
I think that when we when we talk about what happened to us today and we say what terrible thing our
我认为，当我们谈论今天发生在我们身上的事情时，我们会说我们发生了什么可怕的事情
boss did or we talk about the great thing that happened last week on our vacation and we share the unexpected
老板做了，或者我们谈论了上周假期发生的伟大事情，我们分享了意想不到的事情
thing where the unexpected maybe the unexpected person we met.
出人意料的事情也许是我们遇到的出人意料的人。
That's a story.
那是一个故事。
And if you're able to lay out not only the details of the story but also express your emotions and your
如果你不仅能够布置故事的细节，还能表达你的情绪和你的
feelings and the things that happened in a way that are really interesting people are going to want
感觉和以一种非常有趣的方式发生的事情是人们想要的
to focus on you right.
专注于你吧。
So in this class we're going to be talking about progress and we're going to try to make it more like
所以在这堂课上，我们将谈论进步，我们将努力让它更像
more like a story.
更像一个故事。
OK progress means something usually is moving forward and getting better.
好的进展意味着某些事情通常正在向前发展并变得更好。
When we talk about progress we don't talk about things getting worse.
当我们谈论进步时，我们不会谈论事情变得更糟。
We talk about things getting better whether it's our culture maybe it's our culture maybe it's education
我们谈论事情变得更好，无论是我们的文化，也许是我们的文化，也许是教育
we're going to focus on progress as a way to as a way to focus ourselves around these skills related
我们将专注于进步，以此作为一种专注于这些相关技能的方式
to telling stories.
讲故事。
And I'm going to share some important vocabulary words we need to know then we're going to talk about
我将分享一些我们需要知道的重要词汇，然后我们将讨论
a couple of tips and then we'll look at an example so that you can get a feeling about how to do that
一些提示，然后我们将看一个示例，以便您了解如何做到这一点
so that you can actually see the tips and the words that we're going to learn in action.
这样您就可以真正看到我们将在行动中学习的技巧和单词。